{"creationDate":"2018-04-28 11:57:51","type":"questionnaire","id":"qc98bnus7lsjgc7thdt","title":"Bricomarché otros numéros 2017","questions":[{"id":"epobsgiyuasjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Remuneraçao dirigent (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bvclqzdd23njgc7thdt","answer":"1.74","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"g3s96u63dsjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Total encorgos (sin remuneraçao dirigente %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5n4dq2oyj54jgc7thdt","answer":"19.47","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"5l4pyp1q35gjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"costos de pessoal (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"y9d9ww4c128jgc7thdt","answer":"6.90","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"g4bh6u7qac5jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Descontos DDD (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0ieisupna0ljgc7thdt","answer":"0.32","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"3un7r4z835jjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Descontos base (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yrsnrbz3fmjgc7thdt","answer":"0.15","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"akdu4jpbfjejgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Descontos clientes (-%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"12h6s4eyizmjgc7thdt","answer":"-0.31","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"4kdll4v9yxvjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Investimento total (o todo)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bb1fuc5myohjgc7thdt","answer":"3210237","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"r3ni93u6bpjgc7thdt","answer":"3 210 237","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"f8titng7a94jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Renda 3e ano","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"co8ofn9bcuijgc7thdt","answer":"170139","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"36x1lho9ym2jgc7thdt","answer":"170 139","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"qfit9obzr8jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Investimento material","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"n0hntv0ckujgc7thdt","answer":"469341","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"nvojrsehmesjgc7thdt","answer":"469 341","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"opgybmyvrfjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Investimento 2nd obra","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"h0o8i17ir2ejgc7thdt","answer":"341746","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"bwzsg3dbdoajgc7thdt","answer":"341 746","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"wz8s70n466jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Total investimento adherente","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rfiwashotkcjgc7thdt","answer":"900920","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"835y4nq8e8gjgc7thdt","answer":"900 920","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"npzt60vid2jjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Stock (€)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ppt6502k74ajgc7thdt","answer":"915000","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"w6n2u3yns6jgc7thdt","answer":"915 000","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"4rzx76y2l46jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Cotisaçao ITM (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"lum6anz2wfjgc7thdt","answer":"0.84","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"exy4bpqzpsmjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Cotisaçao UDM","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0f0dwoxzzyjgc7thdt","answer":"0.06","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"bah97utce7tjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Area de venta","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0qspwiksb7fqjgc7thdt","answer":"2425","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"ncwpe78yeaajgc7thdt","answer":"2 425","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"6w4t1go9fjvjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Numero de collaboradors","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yl9bd5qdpljjgc7thdt","answer":"22","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"x2esmv5y7ypjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Lugares de parque","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"l98zb5kmt3jgc7thdt","answer":"100","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"vtp58tdjksjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Volume de negocio","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ozqr8yi544jgc7thdt","answer":"4200000","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"3ky7j5hjy0vjgc7thdt","answer":"4 200 000","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"nk21vpdc7bnjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numeros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Stock (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8157zgwu6owjgc7thdt","answer":"21.79","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"m8vk2gyl589jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Terreno total, parque incluido (m²)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bn0rbwuayefjgc7thdt","answer":"9125","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"a326er06mz6jgc7thdt","answer":"9 125","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Bricomarché otros numéros 2017"},{"id":"a8zqmlzuc84jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Aréa de construçao (sim incluido)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"9yxvj24z22jgc7thdt","answer":"2356","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"qzat4md58enjgc7thdt","answer":"2 356","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"7uk0ddw6z0mjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Despesas instalaçao","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"b4a5f9g6lqujgc7thdt","answer":"90833","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"hymy9zh775jgc7thdt","answer":"90 833","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"b1k2p332v7rjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Apport","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5e8iy9p6izhjgc7thdt","answer":"105000","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"ccjupml32sujgc7thdt","answer":"105 000","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"sisd7e1di0bjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Margem antes rémuneraçao do dirigente (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"b8fejhfxo4ejgc7thdt","answer":"6.72","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"n3c7f00u4orjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Margem antes impostes (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"g5oy3kfwamtjgc7thdt","answer":"4.97","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"lykdy7ublzsjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Margem despues discontos","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6mi27rdqs9jjgc7thdt","answer":"25.95","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1}],"fileName":"qc98bnus7lsjgc7thdt.json","modificationDate":"2018-04-28 20:53:36","disabled":true}